Stephen M Oliveiro 2281 Table Rock Rd Apt. 52, Medford, OR 97501 541-973-5877

rotaryraver@gmail.com

Skills Summary

I have over 8 years of computer hardware and software support and maintenance experience. I have worked with both residential and business clientele, both at a store front as well as onsite with the customer. I have a familiarity with many common business applications, including the Microsoft Office suites, QuickBooks and email software. Many times have I worked in high pressure environments where minimal business downtime was critical.

Work Experience

Computer Guys Service Center

Medford, OR May 2011- March 2012

Tech Manager / Head Technician

- Diagnose and Repair windows based systems, both hardware and software
- Go onsite and perform networking and repair services
- Malware removal remotely, onsite and in store.
- Install and configure new devices including printers, external backup solutions, etc.
- Provide phone support
- Use LogMeIn and Bomgar to remotely work on PCs
- Build and configure new desktop and laptop systems
- Generate service schedule protocol and oversee implementation
- Develop and apply protocol for repairing systems.
- Order, Receive and Track Inventory

Office Depot

Medford, OR October 2008 - May 2011

Customer Service Specialist II – Tech Department

- Diagnose customer Windows PCs and sell repair services
- Assess needs and sell technology items to customers
- Run register and handle cash
- Implement merchandising planograms
- Sell new PCs based on customer needs

Computer Guys Service Center

Central Point, OR February 2006 - March 2008

Head Technician

- Diagnose and Repair windows based systems, both hardware and software
- Go onsite and perform networking and repair services
- Malware removal, both onsite and in store.
- Install and configure new devices including printers, external backup solutions, etc.
- Provide phone support
- Use Bomgar to remotely work on PCs
- Build and configure new desktop and laptop systems
- Generate service schedule protocol and oversee implementation
- Develop and apply protocol for repairing systems.

PremierWest Bancorp

Central Point, OR March 2005 - January 2006

Marketing Graphic Designer

- Design graphic collateral for print, branch, and internal use
- Distribute marketing collateral to bank branches in Southern Oregon and Northern California
- Coordinate and schedule print advertising, including newspaper and phone directories in both Oregon and California
- Track and log invoices with accounting

CFC Industries

Central Point, OR May 2004 - March 2005

Computer Support Technician

- Diagnose and repair windows based systems, both hardware and software
- Go onsite and perform networking and repair services
- Malware removal, both onsite and in store.
- Install and configure new devices including printers, external backup solutions, etc.
- Provide phone support
- Build and configure new desktop and laptop systems
- Generate service schedule protocol and oversee implementation
- Develop and apply protocol for repairing systems.

ComputerCom.Com

Phoenix, AZ November 2002 - March 2004

Computer Support Technician

- Diagnose and repair windows based systems, both hardware and software
- Build and Configure new PCs
- Plan, configure, and implement PC networks, both home and business
- Phone tech support for clients
- Onsite tech support and repair
- Cash handling

Education

Associates of Science – Graphic Design and Digital Animation High-Tech Institute, Phoenix, AZ November 2003

References

Gary Arnold, Assistant Store Manager, Office Depot	541-301-7291
Chris Perkins, Former Manager, Computer Guys Service Center	541-944-5249
Sean Bailey, Owner, A-440 Recording	541-944-1074
Jason Holman, Former Manager, Computer Guys Service Center	541-951-9847